(Howard:)Your call.
(Bernadette:)Howard...
(Bernadette:)have you ever considered us
living together?
(Howard:)Boy, I don't know.
(Howard:)You, me, Ma living
under the same roof?
(Bernadette:)No, I mean just you and me.
(Bernadette:)You can move in here,
(Bernadette:)or we can find a place.
(Howard:)I've got a better solution.
What?
(Howard:)We wait for my mom's heart
to explode
(Howard:)from all the salt she eats.
(Howard:)Then we just stick her in
the ground, flip her mattress
(Howard:)and move into the big bedroom.
(Bernadette:)Great.
(Howard:)Look at us planning
a future together!
Who's there?!
(Mrs Wolowitz(voice):)Are you a
sex criminal?!
(Howard:)Sex criminals
don't have keys, Ma!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)Where were you
so late?!
I was out with Bernadette!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I know what
that means!